Alireza Kavian

C.E.O at Brilacasck

Website:

https://alirezakay.github.io

Email:

alireza.kavian7@gmail.com

*PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am also known as @alireza_kay or @alirezakay on social networks.

So far, I've passed **3 years of university**.

I'm busy with the college on 5 days of a week; In free times, I do learn more about my favourite fields like web development Or researching on the relevant issues.

I gained experience through various projects of University in several fields of #CE

I have developed my own company website and blog.

To know more about my works, take a look at Brilacasck company.

I'd like to expand my experiences, every day:) I'd like to study in ' **University Of Toronto** ' in Canada OR ' **ETH Zurich** ' in switzerland one day

* EXPERIENCE

July 2017 -Present

C.E.O at Brilacasck

Chief Execution Officer

Brilacasck

In **2017** I founded this company with my friend.

To gain more experience, we have done diverse projects in different fields of our courses together in university.

Then after a year another friend ours, got joined to our small team.

After that we are a team of tree, a self-employed organization working in the way of **Agile developing** and servicing to our clients/customers

July 2018 -Present

Developer Internship at Ysorkh

Developer

Ysorkh

This would be my internship in the fields of **Network Security**, **Web Security**, **Web SEO** and **Web Development** for deciding what to be the best in my concentration and orientation in Computer Engineering.

* EDUCATION

2015 - Present

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering,

In 2015, I got entered to the university with great inducements for progressing Till now my total average grade is $\bf 18.43$ (of 20)

KNTU University In Tehran, Iran

* SKILLS

Global Skills

- Scrum Project Management
- Team Management
- Idea Performer
- Teaching
- Soccer (GoalKeeping | Defending)
- Ping-Pong

Programming

• Industry Knowledge

- Front-End Development
- Web Development
- Software Engineering
- AVR Programming
- PhotoShop
- o 3D Max
- Microsoft Office (powerpoint word excel)
- Agile Developing

Tools And Technologies

- Javascript
- CSS
- Linux
- HTML
- JQuery
- ReactJS
- AngularJS
- Bootstrap
- o PHP
- SQL
- Python
- 。 C
- ∘ C++
- Intel X86 Assembly (NASM)
- AVR Assembly
- Android
- VHDL

* CERTIFICATIONS

November 2017

Web Designing (Front-End)

University Of Tehran

Using HTML CSS JS JQuery

* VOLUNTEERINGS

Octobor 2017 to January 2018 K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Science And Technology

Role: **Undergraduate Teaching Assistant**Course: Theory of Language and Automaton

Professor: Dr. S.H. Khaasteh

February 2018 to June 2018 K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Science And Technology

Role: Undergraduate Teaching Assistant

Course: Compiler

Professor: Dr. S. Sedighian Kashi.

February 2018 to June 2018 K. N. Toosi University of Technology

Science And Technology

Role: Undergraduate Teaching Assistant

Course: Assembly Language (x86 Intel assembly language)

Professor: Dr. B. Nasihatkon

* PROJECTS

Term 1 - 2015

Simulating A Simple Text Editor With C Language

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term1

Using c and c++ language and also BGI graphical library in my first main programming project

Term 2 - 2016

Simulating Graphical Plant Grwoth In Java

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term2

Using OOP (object oriented programming) in java Language and also graphical java

framework JavaFX

Term 2 - 2016

Implementing DFS/BFS Algorithms In Java

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term2

Using java / javaFX to perform this algorithms to an non-directed graph

Term 3 - 2016 Implementing A Simple Java Compiler In Java

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term3

A simple compiler for java language for detecting typical errors with CFG (context

free grammars)

Implemented with java language

A duo team.

Term 4 - 2017 Implementing A Graphical Chess Game In Java

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term4

A quite pleasant graphical chess game implemented by java language and using JavaFX and Swing (java AWT).

Algorithms: min-max-tree & alpha-beta-game-tree

A duo team.

Term 4 - 2017 Simulating A Plenary CPU Using MIPS Concepts In VHDL

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term4

A MIPS-like processor implemented in VHDL language. (RISC CPU)

Term 5 - 2017 Creating A Full Compiler With Java

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term5

Using compiler concepts to create a full compiler for parsing any languages you want to create.

Using java and JavaFX

A duo team.

Term 5 - 2017 Creating A Shoping Website Using LAMP Stack

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term5

A Website like: digikala For Course: Database

With PHP, MySQL, Apache, Bootstrap

A trio team.

Term 6- 2018 Simulating Micro Communication With Accelerator In SystemC Language

https://github.com/alirezakay/micro-acc-systemc

Communication between micro-processor and accelerator with shared memory in a bus context.

Using SystemC language for hardware-software co-design simulation

A duo team

March 2018 to June 2018 Website: Tiny Courseware Sysrtem For Computer Engineers (TCS4CE)

www.brilacasck.ir:3000

This project was going to implement for the course **Software Engineering.**

I started implementation with my two other team workers. a trio team.

It was a good chance to expose the result of this project to the authorities of our college.

This project is a system for creating courses by teachers / compiling and running codes by students and get score at the same moment

* LANGUAGES

Persian

(Native),

Arabic

(Limited working proficiency),

English

(Professional working proficiency)